(Sheldon:)You forgot your flash drive
You forgot your flash drive
(Howard(steeling himself to talk to Summer Glau, to himself):)It's hot in here. Must be Summer.
(Howard(steeling himself to talk to Summer Glau, to himself):)So, where you gals headed?
Okay, I've found the perfect solution.
We get off the train at the next stop
in Oxnard.
We then take the 1: 13 train
back to Union Station.
We take a cab back,
get my flash drive...
...and race to San Luis Obispo, assuming
the lights are with us, minimal traffic...
...we'll meet the train.
- I've got a better idea.
- Are you going to be sarcastic?
(Leonard:)Boy, you take all the fun out of it for me.
(Leonard:)But, look, Penny's home.
Why don't we call her, have her get
your flash drive and e-mail you the paper?